(upbeat music)
♪ Girl, close your eyes ♪
♪ Let that rhythm get into you ♪
♪ Don't try to fight it ♪
♪ There ain't nothing that you can do ♪
♪ Relax your mind ♪
♪ Lay back and groove with mine ♪
♪ You gotta feel that heat ♪
♪ And we can ride the boogie ♪
♪ Share that beat of love ♪
♪ I wanna rock with you ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ Dance you into day ♪
♪ Sunlight ♪
♪ I wanna rock with you ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ We're gonna rock the night away ♪
(upbeat music continues)
♪ Out on the floor ♪
♪ There ain't nobody there but us ♪
♪ Girl, when you dance ♪
♪ There's a magic that must be love ♪
♪ Just take it slow ♪
♪ 'Cause we got so far to go ♪
♪ When you feel that heat ♪
♪ And we're gonna ride the boogie ♪
♪ Share that beat of love ♪
♪ I wanna rock with you ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ Dance you into day ♪
♪ Sunlight ♪
♪ I wanna rock with you ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ We gon' rock the night away ♪
♪ Rock, right ♪
♪ And when the groove is dead and gone ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ You know that love survives ♪
♪ So we can rock forever ♪
♪ On ♪
(upbeat music continues)
♪ I wanna rock with you ♪
♪ I wanna groove with you ♪
♪ Wanna rock ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ With you, girl ♪
♪ Sunlight ♪
♪ Rock with you, rock with you ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Dance the night away ♪
♪ Rock, right ♪
♪ I wanna rock with you, yeah ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ Rock you into day ♪
♪ Sunlight ♪
♪ I wanna rock with you ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ Rock the night away ♪
♪ Rock, right ♪
♪ Feel the heat, feel the beat ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Rock you into day ♪
♪ Sunlight ♪
♪ I wanna rock ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ Rock the night away ♪
♪ Rock, right ♪